Now the courage to teach is on many many levels
我认为教学勇气体现在很多很多层面，
I think the one that comes most quickly to me
我认为，伴随我很长时间的
that's been with me for a long time has to do with the fact
最快浮现于脑海的是这样一个事实，
that our educational system is so riddled with fear.
即我们的教育系统是如此充斥着恐惧。
Fear is what we use to quote motivate
恐惧是我们引用来刺激
young children to learn
小孩子们去学习的东西，
as if we didn't know
好像我们不知道
that young children are natural learners,
他们是天然的学习者，
that young children are curious,
他们充满好奇，
young children want to probe everything.
他们想探究一切。
Hang around with a four or five year old for a while
和一个四五岁的孩子相处一段时间，
and what do you get question after question
你会听到一个又一个的问题，
after question after question
没完没了的问题，
why, how, what, who.
如为什么、怎么、什么、谁之类的问题。
And yet somehow we get into them into schools.
但不知为何，我们把他们送进学校。
And after a few years we think we have to use
几年后，我们认为我们必须
fear to motivate them to learn.
用恐惧来刺激他们学习。
Now you sit down and do this
我们会告诉他们，坐下来学习，
or you're going to flunk the test,
否则你就会考试不及格，
you're going to fall behind Johnny or Susie,
就会落后于约翰尼或苏西，
you're not going to get to go to college,
上不了大学，
you're not going to have a good life.
过不上美好的生活。
We use fear as an inducement
我们用恐惧作为诱因，
and of course all we induce is paralysis,
可想而知，我们所诱发的是瘫痪，
paralysis of the spirit, paralysis of the mind.
精神的瘫痪以及思想的瘫痪。
So in the middle of all that fear,
因此，在所有这些恐惧中，
it takes courage to teach because
教学需要勇气，
the teacher has to penetrate the student's fears,
因为老师必须穿透学生的恐惧，
the teacher has to create an alternative reality
老师必须创造一个另类现实，
to the one being created by the school system
而不是由学校系统或
or the world around the child.
孩子周遭世界所创造的现实。
And that takes a lot of courage,
这需要很大的勇气，
that means you're swimming up stream,
意味着你要逆流而上，
you're going across the grain
要横下一条心，
and it takes guts to do that.
这样做是需要勇气的。
The other reason
教学需要勇气的
it takes courage to teach or another reason
另一个原因是，
is that teachers have their own fears,
老师们有他们自己的恐惧，
they fear that they can't,
他们担心自己无法应对，
they fear that they're holding something
他们担心自己手里
so precious in their hands, the life of this child or
握着如此珍贵的东西——孩子的生命
and or the subject that they're teaching
以及他们所教的科目，
which most of us who teach take very seriously,
大多数教书的人都非常认真，
that they can't do justice to these treasures.
他们无法对这些珍宝做出公正的处理。
And so you teach with trembling knees,
因此，你在教书时膝盖发抖，
you're always feeling inadequate to the task.
总觉得自己无法胜任这项任务。
And it takes courage to come back
日复一日地回到
day after day after day
这种感觉需要勇气，
to that sense that there's a gap
即你所能做的
between what you're able to do
和这些孩子身上的潜力
and the potential that's in these kids and
之间存在着差距，
how you want them to look at the world
你希望他们通过你的学科
through the lens of your discipline or your subject.
或科目的视角来看待世界。
So those are some of the reasons it takes courage
这些是教学需要勇气的一些原因，
to teach, additionally it takes courage
此外，还需要勇气
to deal with administrators who don't understand
来应对那些不理解教学
what teaching is really about,
真正意义的行政人员，
it takes courage to deal with politicians
需要勇气来应对那些声称
who claim to be putting forth policies
提出了符合我们孩子
that are in the best interests of our children,
最佳利益的教育政策的政客们，
but which aren't, policies that in fact
但这些政策并非如此，事实上，
are smear in the best interests
这些政策是抹黑宣传这些
of the politicians promoting them,
政策的政客的最佳利益，
ways of manipulating public opinion
是他们操纵公众舆论
to get elected to office.
以获得当选的方法。
I call it evil when the claim is
当声称这是为了孩子们的利益时，
that this is for the sake of the children.
我称其为邪恶。
And in fact it's for the sake of
而事实上，这是为了
getting some grown up selected to office
让一些成年人被选入政府办公室，
and giving them lots of perks while the children
并给他们很多福利好处，
are getting crushed in the process.
而孩子们在这个过程中却被压垮。
I think that's a reasonable description of social evil
我认为这是对社会邪恶的合理描述，
and I think it's what's going on in our society.
我认为这就是我们社会中正在发生的事情。
It takes courage to stand with integrity
在这样的情况下，
in the midst of a situation like that.
站在正直的立场上需要勇气。